Logan Thomas

Senior Associate Data Scientist I

Born 1989 in Mountain View, CA





Experience

Developer

Company A since January 2016 Security Clearance as of Sept 2020.

Frontend Developer

Company B

January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Trainee

Company C

March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.



Education

Master of Arts

March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Bachelor of Science

March 2009 - December 2011

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Projects

turkey-bowl

Python

Thanksgiving tradition -Mock NFL fantasy football draft.

repo-scrape

Python

GitHub metadata scraping (Hacktoberfest).

python-practice

Python

Collection of personal Python notes, challenges, and scripts.



Contributions

pyjanitor

Pythonic API for elligant data cleaning and method Algorithms in Python. chaining rountines on pandas DataFrames. https://github.com/ericmj

I/pyjanitor

deap

Distributed Evolutionary https://github.com/DEAP/ deap

pint

Python package to define, operate and manipultae physical quantities - the product of a numerical value and a unit of measure.

https://github.com/hgrec co/pint

About me

I'm a highly motivated and naturally curious individual with 6 years of experience using data science & machine learning techniques. I exhibit an analytical and detail-oriented nature, while placing strong value on building relationships.

Skills

R Python Spark SQL

NumPy **Pandas** scikit-learn

PyTorch TensorFlow

Security Clearance

Contact

6749 Catania Loop

✓ logan.thomas005@gmail.com

(321) 961-9107

in logan-thomas

loganthomas